チ!!
As Gon was dedicating all of his
power to finishing off Neferpitou, Meruem, Pouf, and Youpi were
手段を選ばず …ということで よろしいのですかな？ そこは　君
Flash x And x Start
承知しました。 絶対にアリは　根絶やしにして
Something is missing...
批判は全て　ハンター協会がかぶれ ということですな
But what is it?
キ…　キメラアントは 女王を頂点に
I know...
５つの階級で こ…　構成されています。
I won't say anything. I agree that we shouldn't let the King see her.
うん。 女王がいて その下に直属護衛隊
Ideally, he should stay as he is now. I have
さらに　その下に師団長。
a feeling that something is
missing from this place.
師団長は さらに兵隊長を総括し 兵隊長の下には　多くの雑務兵と 戦闘兵が控えてるってわけね。 そそそ… そして王が生まれると
Though it may just be a side
effect of my memory loss.
その階級がこのように分裂します。
Exactly... Your memory can be verified
through what you see.
女王についていた 直属護衛隊は そのまま王に仕えるってわけね。
Which means you can recover all
of the memories you need.
そそそ…　それに伴い 女王の下には師団長がつき
I believe the selection was to begin at 12:00.
兵隊長や雑務兵を 総括することになります。
Yes. However, that can be moved up.
そして　女王は城に永住し 一定の周期で王を生む。
By 9:00, the remaining humans will be gathered
in the plain before the palace.
王は放浪しながら さまざまな生物と交配し
What is it?
次世代の女王を 次々はらませるわけね。
I have not used my scales on the humans still on their way in.
キメラアントの増殖を 防ぐには
We don't want them to cause a commotion, so I will summon my clones to hypnotize them.
王を生む前に 女王を倒すのが必須条件ね。
What will you do, Youpi?
でも　女王を倒すには
Right... I'll look for Pitou.
周りを固める兵を まず　全て払わないと。 茨の道だな。
Right now, I don't have the
strength to protect you.
[TEL]
Pitou...
うん。
Did you just remember something?
Oh, yeah... We haven't told
the King about Pitou yet.
分かった　待ってる。 討伐隊の第１陣が来るよ。
Meruem-sama, do you remember who Pitou is?
討伐隊？ どんな人達だろう？
Yes, one of my three Royal Guards.
相手は　かなり凶暴な キメラアントだからな。 相当な使い手だろう。 じゃなきゃ　困る！ カイト達が心配だもの。
I can recall Pitou's appearance so clearly, it seems a mystery that I
didn't remember it until now.
到着は３日後よ。
So words can also trigger his memory, not just images...
ハッハッハハハ…！
We must be very careful...
ハッハッハッハッハッ…！
The key will be convincing Pitou.
見ろよ！　すげぇだろ！
I know... Tell Pitou to keep quiet, right?
きっかけが！
There it is again...
((ジャン！　ケン！
I'm counting on you.
グ!!))
Yes... I...
)
asked Pitou to do something for me.
うお!!
Youpi.
ち　か　ら　が…　みなぎるぜ！
Yes... Bring Pitou to me at once.
ペギー。 ん？
Yes.
言っただろ　人間にできるなら 俺達にも　できるとな。
What will you do, Meruem-sama? Enemies are still around.
この不思議な力もか？ いや　しかし　これは…。
Indeed...
ラモット　その状態で俺を殴れ。
As I search for Pitou myself, I shall hunt down the remaining intruders.
な…　何を言っとる？
This is bad!
フッ　あんたにゃ 少なからずムカついてるし
Your Majesty, that would be... It is merely for entertainment.
多分　手加減しねえぜ。 恐らく それぐらいでないと意味がない。
And I am sure these enemies
have useful information.
じゃ　遠慮なく 行かせてもらうぜ。
However, we won't be at your side, and we don't know what enemies remain—
ぬぉ!!
I want an honest answer, Pouf.
おら!!
Do you believe there is a chance
グハっ！ コルト！
that these intruders could get the better of me?!
捕獲せよ
Absolutely not.
生死は問わない
Th-This exceeds my expectations...
ハギャ様。 何だ？
is the ultimate being.
奴らに　やれますかね？ 兵隊長クラスが　束になりゃ そこそこ　いい勝負するだろ。
That much is certain!
でも　あいつら 協力しないと思いますよ。
The overwhelming aura
それなら　それでいい。 それは　また　なぜ？ 俺達が到着するまでの時間稼ぎだ。
left Knuckle and the rest, still concealed, in total despair.
あっ　なるほど！
Th-This isn't something we can deal with...
レアものは　バッチリ 我々が頂くというわけですね。 フンっ　そういうことだ。
To handle this, you'd need an entire
nation's military might. Meleoron, we're making a run for it!
囲まれてる。
But if you and I team up... We could land one attack, sure.
かなりの数だ。
And we could probably attach APR.
さて 順番とやり方を決めようか。
The enemy knows about our powers! They can prepare for us.
ターゲットのお三方 君達には３つの選択権がある。 １　戦う順番を決める。
I was an idiot. We needed to notify the Association
right away of the chairman's defeat, so they could immediately initiate
the next plan of action.
２　逃亡を試みる。
Hurry!
３　諦めて我々に捕まる。
Revenge and duty...
１を選べば　我々の誰かと １対１での戦闘となり
The difference in motivations
between Meleoron and Knuckle
生き残るチャンスもある。
placed growing distance between
them as they walked.
２は　お勧めしない 我々の機嫌を損ねるし
At that moment...
その結果　無残な姿で捕まり 長く苦しむことになる。 ３は　絶対やめたほうがいい。
Meruem's En lit up the palace and the
surrounding area in a literal flash.
キシシシ…。 さて　どうする？ カイト。
Sensing there were two enemies nearby,
he began with Knuckle.
願ってもない話だぞ。
Next was Meleoron, who had barely thought
兵隊長とのタイマンだ。 覚悟が決まったほうから やってみろ。
that he should activate his power
when he was knocked out.
最初はグ ジャン　ケン　ポン！
Where's the King?
よし　俺が行く。
I shall be interrogating them.
人間の特性が 色濃く残る反面
There were two other Nen users whose aura
アリの統率性が失われている
reacted to my En.
俺達にとって　これが 追い風となればいいが… さて　こっちも 誰が戦うか決めようか。
One of them must be carrying
the unconscious Komugi. What do I do? What do I do?
ゲヘヘヘ　ラッキ！
I must stop the King... Your Majesty!
あ？　決まってるだろうが。 どっちかが　死ぬまでさ。
If your purpose is entertainment,
shouldn't you take your time? It appears
「参った」とかじゃダメなの？ はぁ？
that you have a proposal.
ん？ ん？　ん？
Yes... Would you be willing
寝ぼけるなよ！ お前は負ければ即　女王様の餌だ。
to engage in a contest with us?
わしを倒さなきゃ お前は１００％死ぬんだよ。
A contest? Again...
うん　俺は　それでいいよ。
A contest...
でも　君は　別に負けても 死ななくていいじゃん。
俺が勝っても 君を食おうとは思わないし。 「参った」で済むなら 君は助かるよ。
A contest...
その代わり　負けた時は
もう人間を食べないって 約束してもらうけど。
What contest?
ギャハハハ…！ 完全にナメられてるぜ！ 今までで一番 生きのいい相手じゃねえか。
Youpi and I will search for Pitou, while you search for the
two remaining Nen users.
よかったな　バロちゃん！
A contest to see who locates their target first?
ぶち殺す!!
Yes. But don't you need to go and spread scales?
チッ　うまく逃げたな。
So while I hypnotize the remaining humans, I would request that Meruem-sama wait here.
ならば　これは　どうかな？
It is very clear
また　同じ攻撃？
that the difference in power between you
and the intruders is insurmountable.
カハっ。
That cannot be called entertainment.
ゴン！ 軌道を変えた
Meanwhile, we must find Pitou, who has engaged an enemy that
seems capable of teleportation. And Pitou's current location is unknown.
大丈夫！ ウハハハ…　何で　お前 そんなにタフなんだ。 他の奴は　みんな 口から内臓ぶちまけたんだが…。
To make up for the difference, we request additional time,
as well as one further handicap. One further handicap?
まぁ　いいさ 何度でも食らわせてやるわい。
You are only allowed to use En once more.
わしの追尾弾球 よけるのは　不可能。
How does that sound?
確かに　奴は ゴンの逃げる方向に合わせて
Amusing.
軌道を変えればいいだけ
I accept this contest.
どうする？　ゴン
Thank you very much. Perfect...
小僧！ 殺す前に教えておいてやる。
I can use the extra time to kill that woman!
わしが お前ら人間を殺す一番の理由は 食うためでも 食わすためでもない。 じゃあ　何？
As long as we are playing,
I have a proposal, as well.
楽しいからだ。
If you win, I shall grant each of you a wish.
わしはな　口から内臓が 飛び出る時の音が好きなんだ。
Yes, sir. We are very honored.
ブヒョってな。 下痢にそっくりで かなり笑えるぞ。
And what if you win, Meruem-sama?
全然　笑えないよ。 ケッ　お前もブヒョっと派手に ひねり出しちまいな！
If I win, you will tell me what you are hiding from me.
うっ…。 うん…。
You and I are united as one.
はぁ!! くっ。
Did you think that I could not sense
the guilt that you now feel?
よけずに…。 止めやがった。
However, I sense that your feelings
of loyalty are stronger.
うっ　あっ　あぁ…。 レイザーのスパイクは…。 あっ　ぐっ…。 こんなもんじゃなかったぞ!!
Otherwise, I would have sent
your heads flying long ago.
アギィ!!　ゴプっ！
I am certain you have your reasons.
さぁ　俺達　急いでるんでね。
You will obtain what you desire,
and protect your secret. You could not wish for better terms...
俺の相手は誰？ おい！
Assuming that you beat me.
クッフフフ… 調子に乗るのも今のうち。
Meruem-sama...
俺が地獄を見せてやろう。
I shall immediately begin to spread
scales, and not waste a moment.
いいか？　俺を そこのゴミと一緒にするなよ。 ゴミ？
If we lose, we will tell you everything.
ああ　ゴミだから ゴミって言ったんだ。
I swear it on my life.
ケッ 俺は　そいつの１０倍強いぜ。 何だ　大したことないじゃん。
You do not appear to be treating
this as mere entertainment.
何だと？ ２人とも戦闘体勢に入り
Once Pouf finishes spreading his
scales and returns, I shall begin.
オーラが明らかに力強くなった
Is that acceptable?
実戦向きだな ゴンのほうは　かなりスロースターターで やきもきするが
Yes. Victory goes to whomever returns to
this room with their target first.
これなら　十分　間に合う
If Pitou should return, you are to explain the objective of this contest
王を生む前に 女王へたどり着ける
and order Pitou to hide.
だが　なぜだ？
As you wish.
嫌な予感がする
I shall tell you that the two Nen users my En registered
何かを見落としている
were an octopus and a human
carrying some sort of burden.
そんな　薄く粘っこい不安
No, victory is already assured!
見ろよ！　ペギー
The question is what to do
about Pitou and the woman.
フフフ…　俺は　このエネルギー
Then... Start!
すんげぇぞ　こいつは！ ヒャハハハ…。
Where do you think Pitou went? It'll be fine! Pitou should return soon!
あん？ ちゃんとした使い方を 知ることができれば
Turn around and wait by the west
tower for Pitou's return.
我々が生まれ持つ力と合わせ より強力な武器となるだろう。
Do not allow Pitou near the King! You can't use clones while you
spread your scales, right?
ケッ いちいち細けぇんだよ　おめぇは。
Then you aren't buying us any time.
ザザンが…　ハァ…。
Trust me! I'm begging you!
運が良ければ　まだ 貯蔵庫にいるはずだ。
Unbelievable... Such tremendous aura...
ハァ　ハァ…。 探して保護しろ。
Those two are dead. No, they're still alive.
ぬぅ。
They were only knocked unconscious...
ん？
Where's Gon? Killua's carrying him...
ぬぅ…。
His hair is long?
チィ！
Is it someone else?
うぅ…　ぬぅ？
No, those are the only two
figures in my crystal ball. That is Gon!
キヒヒヒ…。 俺の全身は　硬質の皮膚で 覆われているんだ。
In any case, don't come back here... Please!
その程度の攻撃　何発食らっても 平気なんだよ。
Pouf is spreading scales on the citizens... Are they poisonous?
あぁ　そうかよ。
It would help me more if he'd stay near the King.
ぬぅ…。 んっ。
In any case, he's on the palace's opposite side.
ぐっ。
I must get as far from my
previous location as I can...
えっ　んぐっ…。 うわ…。 デェ！
After that En wave, I immediately used Wink Blue, and the King appeared next to Pouf,
carrying Knuckle and Meleoron.
ぐあっ！
Only a few seconds had passed!
ぐっ…。
Next, he will pursue Ikalgo or me.
こいつより １０倍強い奴はいないの？
The King could be standing behind
me at any moment...
うれしい誤算だ
I must hurry and get farther away...
兵隊長クラスを苦にしない
Before the King uses En again!
やはり杞憂か 俺の不安は
I must go in there!
もう　いい！　わしがやる。
If I'm crossing the plain when he uses En, I won't be able to escape!
トゥルルルル…　２！
If I'm deep underground,
perhaps his En won't reach.
なっ!?
But I'm also trapping myself.
２か　ハズレだ。
There's no reason to expect him not to!
あの鎌　かなり　ヤバいぜ。 ゴン　キルア。
What should I do?
３秒後に上へ跳べ。
What is the right decision?
な…　何じゃ この忌まわしい威圧感…
I thought you might come here... Let's go in! Hurry! Yes, but...
思い出したぞ。
The King is on a whole other level.
これは…
Why do you think their lives were spared?
死！
Um, well...
絶対的強者による搾取！
It's possible that I just want
to think that they're alive...
ん…　あっ。
Probably so they can be exchanged.
消えろ。
I'll set a trap...
この大鎌で使えるのは この技のみで
I'm not going out without a fight.
もちろん　使わない限り 消すことができない。
First, we'll hide the girl in Bizeff's room!
キメラアントの女王が 王を生むのを阻止しようと
A contest...
カイト達３人は　女王の城へと さらに奥へ進む